bitrock.com 2011-05-27

# BitRock :: About Us :: Privacy

We hate spam as much as you do. At BitRock, we will never share your information with any third party. Read below for the details.

### BitRock Privacy Policy

This page explains BitRock's policy (the "Privacy Policy") regarding the collection and use of information that can personally identify you whether you are a first-time or repeat visitor to our website. 

### Information Collection and Use

BitRock Incorporated is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties without your explicit permission.

Recent versions of InstallBuilder include an auto-update capability. when InstallBuilder checks for updates, it will transmit information such as operating system type and InstallBuilder version, in order to determine if a newer version is available. Automatic update checking can be disabled at any time by the user.

### Registration

In order to buy the software, a user must first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information such as name, email address, company name, company website and country.

### Log Files

We use IP addresses, browser type, operating system, referring URLs, page views, and access times to analyze trends, administer the site, etc. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Part of this information is gathered using a tracking cookie set by the [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/) service and handled by Google as described in their [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). See your browser documentation for instructions on how to disable the cookie if you prefer not to share this data with Google.

The use of Google Adwords technology allow us to track at an aggregate level which ads are most effective in bringing people to our site.

### Correction/Updating

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code,) or if a user no longer desires our services, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done by emailing us at info@bitrock.com. 

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
